sportschatplace.com 2019-04-17

# Copyright & Privacy Policy | Sports Chat Place

Sports Chat Place posts and supporting documents are owned, held, or licensed by the the Sports Chat Place LLC, and are available for free personal, non-commercial, and educational use, provided that ownership of the materials is properly cited. Any commercial use of the materials, without the written permission of the Sports Chat Place LLLC, is strictly prohibited. If you need additional information about copyright and use of a specific digital collection created at the Sports Chat Place, please contact us [here](https://sportschatplace.com/contact-us-2).

Sports Chat Place LLC is not, under any circumstances, responsible for the unauthorized use or redistribution of digital collections found on this web site.

## Legal Notice:

Activities offered by advertising links to other sites may be deemed an illegal activity in certain jurisdictions. Viewers are specifically warned that they should inquire into the legality of participating in any games and/or activities offered by such other sites. The owner of this website assumes no responsibility for the actions by and makes no representation or endorsement of any of these games and/or activities offered by the advertiser. As a condition of viewing this website viewers agree to hold the owner of this website harmless from any claims arising from the viewer’s participation in any of the games and/or activities offered by the advertiser.

## **Privacy Policy**

### What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

### What do we use your information for? 

#### ****Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  ****

****; To personalize your experience****  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

**; To process transactions**

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

**; To send periodic emails**

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

### How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we use cookies? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Terms and Conditions 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://sportschatplace.com](http://www2.sportschatplace.com/)

## Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

## Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 10/25/17

## Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

https://sportschatplace.com  
Las Vegas, NV  
United States  
Paradise Rd.

Sportschatplace.com may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.networkadvertising.org%2Fmanaging%2Fopt_out.asp&sa=D&sntz=1&usg=AFQjCNGLrN7Q3yfX4kPIuQhtUNKfQMyCNg)

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
